Radoslaw Zuchelkowski

Piaseczno, Mazowieckie, Poland



radek.zuchelkowski@gmail.com



+48600088722



linkedin.com/in/radoslaw-zuchelkowski-050a80

Summary

I am Technical Engineer of Computer Engineering specialty that gave-up his engineering background for sales career. Still not convinced if it was a mistake. With more than 20 years of experience in the area of sales management, working for best SI/IT/SMARTPHONE players on the market, I recently decided to "return to the roots" and complete Red Team Specialist course for Cyber Security professionals (to the courtesy of HackerU/University of Warsaw). It is obvious how sales, especially ever increasing online sales, is closely connected with Cyber Security threats nowadays and it is only a tip of the iceberg called Cyber Security. Personally, I find it very exciting. I am open to possitions in Cyber Security field that will harness my sales expertise and/or let me continue to specialize/job profile in Cyber Security field (SIEM solutions, Red Teaming, Pen Testing, Mobile Security, etc.). I am a result oriented, communicative, analytical approach individual. In all my work environments I always tried to bring a dose of humour because I believe it eases the negative effects of operating under stress for a long time.

Experience



Senior Sales/Retail KAM

OPPO

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

- Managing sales of CES account RTV Euro AGD ("Euro-net" Sp. z o.o.)
- Product Group: smartphones, IOT



Senior Sales/Retail KAM

Samsung Electronics Polska

Aug 2014 - Jan 2021 (6 years 6 months)

- Managing sales of CES account Mediaexpert (TERG S.A.)
- Responsibility for Team of 1 Sales Specialist
- Product Group: smartphones, tablets, wearables, accessories

SAMSUNG

Sales Manager (B2C Reseller)

Samsung Electronics Polska

Feb 2011 - Aug 2014 (3 years 7 months)

- Managing B2C Reseller Channel (S/M computer re-seller shops)
- Responsibility for Team of 3 Sales Specialists
- Product Group: notebooks, monitors, printers



Retail Account Executive

Acer

Apr 2009 - Jan 2011 (1 year 10 months)

• Managing sales of CES account - Mediamarkt (Media Saturn Holding Polska Sp. z o.o.)

• Product Group: notebooks/netbooks, PC's, monitors

© Channel Sales Manager (notebooks)

LG Electronics

Feb 2005 - Feb 2009 (4 years 1 month)

- · Coordinated all sales channels (resellers, CES) to achieve overall notebook sales target
- · Cooperated with distributors and dealers (ABC Data, Action, Pronox, Incom, NTT, Komputronik, etc.)
- · Cooperated with retail chains (Media-Saturn, Avans, Mediaexpert, Mix, Domator, etc.)
- Created and introduced promotion marketing plans to achieve quarterly sales target (demo programs for resellers, promotions, motivational programs for distributors, dedicated sales programs for resellers)
- Set and executed monthly sales targets (distributors)
- Cooperated with marketing department in terms of ATL/BTL activities (web site product contents, press ads, product placement, tests, product catalog, etc.)
- Prepared product trainings and presentations for all sales channels
- · Recruited and manages sales promoters team of 11 persons

Key Account Manager

Comarch

Aug 2003 - Feb 2005 (1 year 7 months)

- •Realized sales target
- Proactively acquired new clients
- •Strengthened the relationship with existing clients
- Provided technical support

Education

University of Warsaw

RED TEAM SPECIALIST, Cybersecurity

Nov 2021 - Jun 2022

- האקריו המרכז ללימודי מחשבים והשמת עובדים בהייטק

Red Team Specialist, Cybersecurity

Nov 2021 - Jun 2022

W Walsh College

MBA

1999 - 2001

Michigan, USA

West Pomeranian University of Technology in Szczecin

MSE

1993 - 1998

Szczecin, Poland

Skills

SIEM & SOC (SIEM & SOC Introduction, End-Point Protection, Network Protection & Prevention, Windows Live & Offline Analysis, Memory Analysis, Basic Static Analysis, Log Generation & Collection, SIEM Solutions, IOC & Malwares, Basic Dynamic Analysis) • BYPASSING THE PERIMETER (WireShark, MITM, OSINT & Social Engineering, Network Scanning, Password Cracking, MetaSploit &Known CVEs, Wi-Fi Attacks, Web Anonymity) • WEB APPLICATION PENETRATION TESTING (Web Technologies, PHP Vulnreabilities & OWASP Top 10, Burp & ZAP, XSS, Database Management, SQL Injection, Advanced SQL Injection, NoSQL Injection, CSRF & Broken Authentication, XXE & SSRF, LFI/RFI to RCE & WordPress Hacking, PT Flow & Reporting and Vulnerabilities Scanning) • LINUX FUNDAMENTALS (Introduction to Linux, Users, Groups & Permissions, Network Configuration & Package Management, Configuring Services) • WINDOWS SERVER 2016 (Creating an Organization, Active Directory Management, Working with Services (DHCP & DNS), GPO Management) • CROSS PLATFORM ELEVATION OF PRIVILEGES (Windows Local Privilege Escalation, Windows Post Exploitation & Credentials Dumping, Linux Local PE & Post Exploitation, Linux Automated Tasks & Permission Misconfiguration, Common Exploits & Buffer Overflow, Unquoted Services & DLL Hijacking) • ADVANCED INFRASTRUCTURE (Enumerating an Organization, Lateral Movement, Obfuscation Techniques, Office Exploitation, Exploiting Services within an organization, SMB Relay & Responder, PowerShell as a Weapon, Reverse Shells & Tunneling, Kerberoasting & Pass the Ticket & Module Review) • PYTHON FOR HACKING (Introduction to Python, Data Types & Loops, Functions & Code Handling, File System & Error Handling, Web Communication, Sockets Fundamentals, Protocols Communication, Scapy & Network Scanning) WEB FUNDAMENTALS (Introduction to HTML, CSS Fundamentals, JavaScript Fundamentals, Building Web Pages, Advanced JavaScript, Introduction to Server-Side) • MOBILE SECURITY (Introduction to Android, Android Programming, Android Reversing, Android Traffic Analysis, SSL Pinning, Android Malwares & Run Time Debugging, Static & Dynamic Investigation Frameworks, iOS Security)